[
  {
    "question": "What is Jayway commited to?",
    "optionA": "Measurable goals",
    "optionB": "Iteration",
    "optionC": "Client relationships",
    "optionD": "Assumptions",
    "answer": "Client relationships"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following companies is a Jayway partner?",
    "optionA": "Amazon Web Services",
    "optionB": "Facebook",
    "optionC": "IMB",
    "optionD": "Volvo",
    "answer": "Amazon Web Services"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following cities has a Jayway office?",
    "optionA": "Madrid",
    "optionB": "Malmö",
    "optionC": "Paris",
    "optionD": "New York",
    "answer": "Malmö"
  },

  {
    "question": "What ideas does Jayway share on their blog?",
    "optionA": "Tech and good practices ",
    "optionB": "Tech and food",
    "optionC": "Tech and insight ideas",
    "optionD": "Tech and organizing",
    "answer": "Tech and insight ideas"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following projects was developed by Jayway?",
    "optionA": "Bill pay",
    "optionB": "Billum pay",
    "optionC": "Telm pay",
    "optionD": "Telia pay",
    "answer": "Telia pay"
  },

  {
    "question": "Does Jayway have an Immersive Lab?",
    "optionA": "You betcha they do!",
    "optionB": "They wish...",
    "optionC": "No",
    "optionD": "I don't know",
    "answer": "You betcha they do!"
  },

  {
    "question": "What did Jayway develop in the Massive entertainment project?",
    "optionA": "A videogame",
    "optionB": "An advertisement",
    "optionC": "A high-quality website",
    "optionD": "A banking app",
    "answer": "A high-quality website"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following companies belong to Jayway's family?",
    "optionA": "Future of Tech",
    "optionB": "Lifehacker",
    "optionC": "Hack a Day",
    "optionD": "Forever Geek",
    "answer": "Future of Tech"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which is a Jayway data principle?",
    "optionA": "Data as a business",
    "optionB": "Data as design",
    "optionC": "Data as a product",
    "optionD": "Data as itiration",
    "answer": "Data as a product"
  },

  {
    "question": "Is Jayway one of the coolest companies to work for?",
    "optionA": "For sure!",
    "optionB": "No way",
    "optionC": "Nope",
    "optionD": "I don't know",
    "answer": "For sure!"
  },

  {
    "question": "What kind of lab is developed in Malmö's Jayway office?",
    "optionA": "VR",
    "optionB": "MongoDB",
    "optionC": "IOT",
    "optionD": "OOP",
    "answer": "VR"
  },

  {
    "question": "How many followers does Jayway have on instagram?",
    "optionA": "Less than 200",
    "optionB": "Between 200 and 300",
    "optionC": "Less than 500",
    "optionD": "More than 500",
    "answer": "For sure!"
  }
]
